aspalliance.com 2002-12-05

# ASPAlliance.com : The #1 ASP.NET Developer Community : Privacy Policy

## Privacy Statement for AspAlliance.com

AspAlliance.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: AspAlliance.com. 

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. We use cookies to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site and for other purposes. 

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address). The customer's contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.

This site contains links to other sites. **AspAlliance.com** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

Our online surveys ask visitors for contact information (like their email address). Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

We run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (like their email address). Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. Our third-party advertising company also separately places or recognizes a cookie file on your browser in the course of delivering advertisements to this Site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click here: <http://www.sonar.com/content/privacy.htm>

## Public Forums

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

## Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. 

## Choice/Opt-Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor. 

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. 

  1. You can send email to [ssmith@aspalliance.com](mailto:ssmith@aspalliance.com)

## Correct/Update

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. 

  1. email [ssmith@aspalliance.com](mailto:ssmith@aspalliance.com)

## Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact Steven Smith AspAlliance.com 1993 Brookview Dr. Kent, OH 44240 ssmith@aspalliance.com
